Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 9]
[الحلقة 9]
I have a shipment.
لدي شحنة.
I'll use your dock.
سأستخدم قفص الاتهام الخاص بك.
Bring it back intact.
أعيدها سليمة.
This is your final chance.
هذه فرصتك الأخيرة.
Do you want to know
هل تريد أن تعرف
who killed the Lin family back then?
من قتل عائلة لين في ذلك الوقت؟
It was my father.
لقد كان والدي.
Your so-called savior.
منقذك المزعوم.
He planned it.
لقد خطط لذلك.
Get the kid out.
أخرج الطفل.
Yes.
نعم.
After the Lin family fire,
بعد حريق عائلة لين،
my father saved you.
لقد أنقذك والدي.
He let you live ten more years
لقد تركك تعيش عشر سنوات أخرى
as Qingmao.
مثل تشينغماو.
From today, you will
من اليوم سوف
enter the Wang family's orphanage for training.
الدخول إلى دار الأيتام لعائلة وانغ للتدريب.
Lin Qingyi,
لين تشينغي,
from now on, you are Qingmao.
من الآن فصاعدا، أنت تشينغماو.
I will help you
سأساعدك
find the one who murdered your family.
ابحث عن الشخص الذي قتل عائلتك.
This time, at any cost,
هذه المرة، بأي ثمن،
the Wang family's crimes must be exposed to the world.
يجب أن يتم الكشف عن جرائم عائلة وانغ للعالم.
Rumeng. Rumeng!
رومينج. رومينج!
Rumeng,
رومينج،
I know you are Qingmao.
أنا أعلم أنك تشينغماو.
But with your strength alone,
ولكن بقوتك وحدها،
how can you take on the entire Wang family?
كيف يمكنك مواجهة عائلة وانج بأكملها؟
Chick, today, this shipment and you
يا كتكوت، اليوم، هذه الشحنة وأنت
are mine to take.
هي ملكي لأخذها.
We'll see
سوف نرى
if you have what it takes.
إذا كان لديك ما يلزم.
Get her!
احصل عليها!
Chen Wenbin!
تشين وينبين!
Look out!
انتبه!
An ugly freak.
غريب قبيح.
An abandoned boy.
صبي مهجور.
I am not abandoned!
أنا لست مهجورا!
My father will come for me!
سيأتي أبي إليّ!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
My face is ugly.
وجهي قبيح.
No, it's not.
لا، ليس كذلك.
The ones who hit you are the ugly ones.
الذين يضربونك هم القبيحون
I'm Su Jinmo.
أنا سو جينمو.
I just came to the orphanage a year ago.
لقد أتيت إلى دار الأيتام منذ عام واحد فقط.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
My name is Lin...
اسمي لين...
My name is Qingmao.
اسمي تشينغماو.
I haven't seen you
لم أرك
around the orphanage lately.
حول دار الأيتام في الآونة الأخيرة.
Are you an orphan too?
هل أنت يتيم أيضاً؟
I live on the back hill.
أنا أعيش في التل الخلفي.
My mom and dad, they both...
أمي وأبي، كلاهما...
We fight side by side today.
نحن نقاتل جنبًا إلى جنب اليوم.
That makes us family.
وهذا ما يجعلنا عائلة.
This Tiger-Head Lock is our pledge.
قفل رأس النمر هو تعهدنا.
I will always protect you.
سأحميك دائمًا.
Su Jinmo, you got candy again!
سو جينمو، لقد حصلت على الحلوى مرة أخرى!
I didn't mean to...
لم أقصد ذلك...
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Candy makes it stop hurting.
الحلوى تجعل الأمر يتوقف عن الألم.
Su Jinmo,
سو جينمو,
come out here for a moment.
تعال هنا للحظة.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Your family is here to pick you up.
عائلتك هنا لالتقاطك.
I... I'm not going!
أنا... أنا لا أذهب!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Jinmo!
جينمو!
Qingmao!
تشينغماو!
Su Jinmo.
سو جينمو.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
You... you're hurt.
أنت... أنت مجروح.
Liu Rumeng,
ليو رومينج,
did you really think you could take the cargo?
هل كنت تعتقد حقا أنك تستطيع أن تأخذ البضائع؟
Only I am authorized to collect
أنا فقط المخول بجمع
the Wang family's cargo.
حمولة عائلة وانغ.
So,
لذا،
you admit this belongs to the Wang family?
هل تعترف أن هذا ينتمي إلى عائلة وانج؟
It does!
إنه كذلك!
Come on, look at the camera.
تعال، انظر إلى الكاميرا.
Everyone, smile!
الجميع، ابتسموا!
Opium trafficking is a serious case.
إن تجارة الأفيون تعتبر قضية خطيرة.
I'm here reporting live for the Song City Daily.
أنا هنا أقوم بتغطية حية لصحيفة Song City Daily.
Before you pin such a serious charge on us,
قبل أن توجه لنا مثل هذه التهمة الخطيرة،
you should see
يجب عليك أن ترى
what's really inside.
ما هو حقا في الداخل.
Tea?
شاي؟
A bit damp.
رطب قليلا.
Liu Rumeng,
ليو رومينج,
you really work hard for other's thing, huh?
أنت تعمل بجد من أجل مصلحة الآخرين، أليس كذلك؟
Thanks to you,
شكرا لك
the Wang family's shipment
شحنة عائلة وانغ
should have arrived safely by now.
كان ينبغي أن يصل بسلامة الآن.
Sir! Sir!
سيدي! سيدي!
The goods have been supplied.
لقد تم توفير البضاعة.
The funds have been covered. Look.
لقد تم تغطية الأموال. انظر.
It seems Liu Rumeng isn't so formidable after all.
يبدو أن ليو رومينج ليس بهذه القوة بعد كل شيء.
At the scene,
في مكان الحادث،
who else was there?
من كان هناك أيضا؟
It was Marshal Chen who called the police.
وكان المارشال تشين هو الذي اتصل بالشرطة.
He protected Miss Liu.
لقد حمى الآنسة ليو.
I knew it was him.
عرفت أنه هو.
Deliver all these funds to the Chen family.
تسليم كل هذه الأموال إلى عائلة تشين.
Wan'er and Wenbin are to be married immediately.
وان إير ووينبين سيتزوجان على الفور.
What about Liu Rumeng?
ماذا عن ليو رومينج؟
Should we still keep watch on her?
هل يجب علينا أن نستمر في مراقبتها؟
Of course, we keep watch.
بالطبع، نحن نستمر في المراقبة.
Right now,
الآن،
she's a bird in a cage.
إنها طائر في القفص.
We must keep her under our eyes.
يجب علينا أن نبقيها تحت أعيننا.
Give her my terms.
أعطيها شروطي.
And she will accept them.
وسوف تقبلهم.
Otherwise, Chen Wenbin
وإلا، تشين وينبين
will die.
يريد ذلك.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Still so fierce, are you?
هل مازلت شرسة جدًا؟
Go on, show me how fierce you are.
إذهب، أرني مدى شراستك.
Marshal Chen,
المارشال تشين،
please control yourself.
من فضلك تحكم في نفسك.
Wenbin!
وينبين!
Dad!
أب!
Dad, hurry up and announce it!
أبي، اسرع وأعلن ذلك!
Look how impatient you are.
انظر إلى مدى نفاد صبرك.
Now that everyone is here,
الآن وقد أصبح الجميع هنا،
I will make the announcement.
سأقوم بالإعلان.
Today
اليوم
is a joyous occasion,
إنها مناسبة سعيدة
a day of double happiness.
يوم من السعادة المزدوجة.
This first blessing
هذه النعمة الأولى
is that...
هل هذا...
Wenbin,
وينبين،
your father has agreed
لقد وافق والدك
to your marriage to Wan'er.
إلى زواجك من وان إير.
Dad, you only mentioned one thing to me.
أبي، لقد ذكرت لي شيئًا واحدًا فقط.
What is the other?
ما هو الآخر؟
As for the second blessing...
وأما النعمة الثانية...
Wenbin, it is also a great occasion for me.
وينبين، إنها أيضًا مناسبة عظيمة بالنسبة لي.
Miss Liu
الآنسة ليو
will shortly become
سوف تصبح قريبا
my concubine.
محظيتي.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪